YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 6. Program: Series V. Program Subjects
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. PROGRAM SUBJECTS
  - Subseries B. Health and Recreation
    - Conferences and Workshops, YWCA
      - Health Education Conferences, 1919-20 (Box 593, Folder 16)
      - Physical Directors' Conferences, 1922-23 (Box 593, Folder 17)
      - Health Education Institutes (aka Camps or Conferences)
        - 1923-33 (Box 593, Folder 18-28)
        - 1935-39, 1941-42 (Box 594, Folder 1-6)
      - Physical Fitness for Women in Industry (USO), 1942 (Box 594, Folder 7)
      - Big Cities Workshop and Counselors Meeting: Total Needs of People, Jan and Mar 1945 (Box 594, Folder 8)
      - Health Education Conference, 1947 (Box 594, Folder 9)
      - Regional HPER Work Groups, 1960 (Box 594, Folder 10)
      - YWCA Dialogue with the Living Arts, Jun 1968 (Box 594, Folder 11)
    - Conferences, non-YWCA
      - International Conference of Women Physicians (hosted by YWCA), Sep 1919
        - Planning (Box 594, Folder 12)
        - Attendance rosters (Box 594, Folder 13)
        - Program (Box 594, Folder 14)
        - Reports (Box 594, Folder 15)
        - Proceedings
          - I. General Problems of Health (Box 594, Folder 16)
          - II. Industrial Health (Box 594, Folder 17)
          - III. The Health of the Child (Box 594, Folder 18)
          - IV. Moral Codes and Personality (Box 594, Folder 19)
          - V. Adaptation of the Individual to Life (Box 595, Folder 1)
          - VI. Conservation of Health of Women in Marriage (Box 595, Folder 2)
      - New Jersey College for Women Vocational Information Conference, 1939 (Edith M. Gates, panelist) (Box 595, Folder 3)
      - Women's Health and Sport Session of the Citizen Ambassador Program U.S./China Joint Conference on Women's Issues, 1995 (Box 595, Folder 4)
      - World Conference on Women and Sport, 1996 (Box 595, Folder 5)
      - Congressional Black Caucus Foundation Legislative Conference, 1997 (Alpha Alexander, speaker) (Box 595, Folder 6)
    - Programs and Projects
      - Health--National
        - Health Week, 1920-23 (Box 595, Folder 7)
        - Skeleton Program, 1920 (Box 595, Folder 8)
        - An Individual Health Program Adapted to Groups, 1920 (Box 595, Folder 9)
        - ENCORE
          - General, 1975-91, n.d. (Box 595, Folder 10)
          - ENCORE News, 1978-82 (Box 595, Folder 11)
          - ENCORE Newsletter, 1984-85 (Box 595, Folder 12)
          - For Women Only-YWCA ENCORE Classic, 1992, n.d. (Box 595, Folder 13)
          - Program Manuals
            - "Program Manual for Community YWCAs"
              - 1980 (Box 595, Folder 14-15)
              - 1983 (Box 596, Folder 1)
            - "Taking the Lead with ENCORE," 1990 (Box 596, Folder 2)
          - Training, 1977-84 (Box 596, Folder 3)
        - National Breast Cancer Awareness Week Clinics and Workshops, 1985-86 (Box 596, Folder 4-5)
        - ENCOREplus
          - General, 1995-99, n.d. (Box 596, Folder 6)
          - Program description, circa 1994 (Box 596, Folder 7)
          - Program evaluation
            - Funding proposals, 1998 (Box 596, Folder 8)
            - "Evaluation of ENCORE plus A Community-Based Breast and Cervical Cancer Screening Program" by Maria E. Fernandez et al, American Journal of Preventive Medicine, 1999; 16 (3S) (Box 596, Folder 9)
            - Evaluation kit, circa 1997 (Box 596, Folder 10)
          - Advisory Board, 1995 (Box 596, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence, 1994-99 (Box 596, Folder 12-13)
          - Consultants
            - Cicatelli Associates, Training Center for Health Professionals, 1994-97 (Box 596, Folder 14)
            - DeBor and Associates, 1995-96, n.d. (Box 596, Folder 15)
            - Macro International, 1994-97 (Box 596, Folder 16)
            - Philliber Research Associates, 1994 (Box 597, Folder 1)
            - Professional Key Punch, Inc., 1997 (Box 597, Folder 2)
            - Stewart, Karen, 1996 (Box 597, Folder 3)
            - University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston, 1997-98 (Box 597, Folder 4)
            - Wughalter, Emily, 1994 (Box 597, Folder 5)
          - Financial
            - Reports, 1996-97 (Box 597, Folder 6)
            - Corporate Partnerships
              - General, 1997 (Box 597, Folder 7)
              - "The Partnership Proposal," 1997 (Box 597, Folder 8)
          - Grants to Member Associations
            - Request for proposal forms and instructions, 1994-97 (Box 597, Folder 9-12)
            - Grant proposal review, 1994-98 (Box 597, Folder 13-15)
            - Standard contract, 1994-95 (Box 597, Folder 16)
            - Agreements and correspondence with Associations, 1994-97 (Box 597, Folder 17-18)
          - ENCOREplus Newsletter, 1996-98 (Box 597, Folder 19)
          - Public Awareness Campaign
            - Press conference, Washington, DC, 27 Apr 1994 (Box 597, Folder 20)
            - ENCORE plus Marketing and Public relations kit, 1996 (Box 597, Folder 21)
            - Race for the Cure, 1996 [national] (Box 597, Folder 22)
            - Breast Cancer Awareness Postage Stamp
              - General, Dec 1995-1996 (Box 598, Folder 1-2)
              - Brochure and cache design, 1996 (Box 598, Folder 3)
              - Press kit, 1996 (Box 598, Folder 4)
              - Local events, 1996 (Box 598, Folder 5-7)
            - The March: Coming Together to Conquer Cancer, 25-26 September 1998 [national]
              - General, 1997-98 (Box 598, Folder 8)
              - Press kit, 1998 (Box 598, Folder 9)
            - Home Box Office documentary "Cancer: Evolution to Revolution," 2000 (Box 598, Folder 10)
            - Peter Drucker Award for Nonprofit Innovation application, 1997 (Box 598, Folder 11)
            - Planet Earth Foundation, 1996-97 (Box 598, Folder 12)
          - Reports
            - Miscellaneous, 1995-97 (Box 598, Folder 13)
            - Annual Reports
              - 1995-96 (Box 598, Folder 14-15)
              - July 1996-98 (Box 599, Folder 1-2)
          - Training
            - General, 1994-96, n.d. (Box 599, Folder 3)
            - Program Implementation Manual: correspondence with reviewers, 1994 (Box 599, Folder 4)
            - ENCOREplus Trainer's Manual, 1994 (Box 599, Folder 5-9)
            - First Annual Conference (aka technical assistance meeting), 16-18 September 1995
              - Program and handouts (Box 599, Folder 10)
              - Planning (Box 599, Folder 11)
              - Exhibitors (Box 600, Folder 1)
              - Registration forms with issues of concern (Box 600, Folder 2)
              - Evaluations (Box 600, Folder 3)
            - Feb 1998
              - Planning (Box 600, Folder 4)
              - Evaluations (Box 600, Folder 5)
            - National Breast Cancer Coalition: Project LEAD Training Courses, 1996 (Box 600, Folder 6)
          - Yearbooks, 1995-96 (Box 600, Folder 7-8)
          - Organizations
            - American Association of Retired Persons, 1995-96 (Box 600, Folder 9)
            - Agency for Health Care Policy and Research, 1995 (Box 600, Folder 10)
            - American Cancer Society, 1994-2000 (Box 600, Folder 11)
            - Avon Products, Inc., [see also National Alliance of Breast Cancer Organizations below]
              - General
                - 1992-95 (Box 600, Folder 12-13)
                - 1996-98, 2001 (Box 601, Folder 1-3)
              - Contracts, 1993-95 (Box 601, Folder 4-5)
              - Financial
                - Budget, 1994-98 (Box 601, Folder 6-9)
                - Reports, 1995-98 (Box 601, Folder 10)
              - News clippings and press releases, 1993-97, n.d. (Box 601, Folder 11)
              - Reports
                - Quarterly, 1994-98 (Box 601, Folder 12)
                - Program Report, Nov 1996 (Box 601, Folder 13)
                - Revisions and replacements, Jan 1997 (Box 602, Folder 1)
            - Breast Care Test Coalition (Pennsylvania YWCAs)
              - General, 1992-96, n.d. (Box 602, Folder 2)
              - Publication: "Breast Care: You Are Your Best Defense," 1996 (Box 602, Folder 3)
            - Gifts in Kind America, 1994-97 (Box 602, Folder 4)
            - National Alliance of Breast Cancer Organizations, 1994-98 (Box 602, Folder 5-6)
            - Partnership for Cancer Control in Underserved Populations Regional Conferences
              - General, 1995-97 (Box 602, Folder 7)
              - Great Lakes Conference, 1997 (Box 602, Folder 8)
            - Susan G. Komen Breast Cancer Foundation
              - General, 1994-98 (Box 602, Folder 9)
              - Komen/Hallmark, Cards for the Cure program, 2000-2001 (Box 602, Folder 10)
          - U.S. Department of Health and Human Services
            - Miscellaneous departments, 1994-97 (Box 602, Folder 11)
            - Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC): National Breast and Cervical Cancer Early Detection Program (NBCCEDP)
              - General, 1992-97, n.d. (Box 602, Folder 12)
              - CDC Orientation Meeting for National Organizations, Apr 1994 (Box 602, Folder 13)
              - CDC National Organizations Program Directors' Meeting, Apr 1996 (Box 602, Folder 14)
              - CDC and YWCA Collaborative Agreement, 1993, n.d. (Box 603, Folder 1)
              - Applications, proposals, and work plans, 1992-97 (Box 603, Folder 2-7)
              - Award notices, 1994-97 (Box 603, Folder 8-11)
              - Conferences, 1994-96 (Box 603, Folder 12)
              - Consultants: Strategic Health Concepts, 1995-96 (Box 603, Folder 13)
              - Correspondence, 1991-2000 (Box 604, Folder 1-2)
              - Financial, 1994-98 (Box 604, Folder 3)
              - Reports, 1995-97 (Box 604, Folder 4)
              - State partnerships, 1993-94 (Box 604, Folder 5)
              - Maryland Partnership (aka Maryland Demonstration Project)
                - General, 1992-95, n.d. (Box 604, Folder 6)
                - Proposals, 1993-94, n.d. (Box 604, Folder 7)
                - Budgets, 1993-95 (Box 604, Folder 8)
                - Reports, 1994-95, n.d. (Box 604, Folder 9)
                - Subcontractor: AMC Cancer Research Center
                - Contract, 1993 (Box 604, Folder 10)
                - Evaluation of program meetings, 1994 (Box 604, Folder 11)
                - Reference materials (Box 604, Folder 12)
                - Case Study "Partnering for Success: State Health Departments Working With Member Associations of the YWCA of the USA"
                - Draft, 1995 (Box 605, Folder 1)
                - Final (?), n.d. (Box 605, Folder 2)
              - Lesbian Demonstration Project (aka Lesbian Outreach Initiative)
                - General, 1994-97, n.d. (Box 605, Folder 3-4)
                - Proposal to CDC and award notifications, 1995 (Box 605, Folder 5)
                - Consultants: Mautner Project for Lesbians with Cancer
                - General, 1995-98, n.d. (Box 605, Folder 6)
                - Contracts, 1995-96 (Box 605, Folder 7)
                - News clippings and press releases, 1995 (Box 605, Folder 8)
                - "Schedule Your Checkup Now," public service announcement, 1997 (Box 605, Folder 9)
                - "Tools for Caring About Lesbian Health"
                - Brochure, 1997-98 (Box 605, Folder 10)
                - Video, 1997-98 (Box 605, Folder 11)
                - Report forms, 1995-97 (Box 605, Folder 12)
                - Final Report, draft, Aug 1997 (Box 606, Folder 1)
                - Sites
                - Request for Proposal forms, 1995-96 (Box 606, Folder 2)
                - Quarterly Reports, 1995-97 (Box 606, Folder 3-9)
                - Year 1 Progress Reports, 1996 (Box 606, Folder 10)
                - YWCA of Bangor-Brewer, Maine, 1995 (Box 606, Folder 11)
                - YWCA of Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1995-96 (Box 606, Folder 12)
                - YWCA of Metropolitan Dallas, Texas, 1995-97 (Box 606, Folder 13)
                - YWCA of Seattle-King County, Washington, 1995-97 (Box 606, Folder 14)
                - YWCA of Tucson, Arizona, 1995-96 (Box 606, Folder 15)
            - National Action Plan on Breast Cancer
              - General, 1995-97 (Box 606, Folder 16)
              - National Institutes of Health: The Secretary's Conference to Establish a National Action Plan on Breast Cancer, 14-15 Dec 1993 (Box 606, Folder 17)
              - Contractor: R.O.W. Sciences, Inc., 1997 (Box 607, Folder 1)
            - Valdez & Associates: Multimedia Breast Cancer Education Kiosks for Latinas, 1997 (Box 607, Folder 2)
        - Just the Facts: What Every Woman Needs to Know about Vaginal Health (aka Bacterial Vaginosis Project)
          - General, 1998-99 (Box 607, Folder 3-4)
          - Workshops
            - General, 2001 (Box 607, Folder 5)
            - Evaluations, Apr 2001 (Box 607, Folder 6)
            - 2002 (Box 607, Folder 7)
        - "Moving Past Trauma" Post Traumatic Stress Disorder Community Outreach, 2001 (Box 607, Folder 8)
        - Sexually transmitted disease programs and Community Associations, list, 1999 (Box 607, Folder 9)
        - "Stay Strong! Test Your Bone Strength" bone density testing campaign with Strong Women Inside and Out
          - General, 2000-01 (Box 607, Folder 10-11)
          - Testing Event Guide, 2000 (Box 607, Folder 12)
      - Recreation
        - Miscellaneous, 1920, n.d. (Box 607, Folder 13)
        - Man and Girl Recreation Activities, circa 1920 (Box 607, Folder 14)
        - Play Institute, Dallas, Texas, YWCA, 1927 (Box 607, Folder 15)
        - Water pageants, 1933, 1937 (Box 607, Folder 16)
        - Training Program for the Arts
          - General, 1977-79, n.d. (Box 607, Folder 17-18)
          - Progress Reports, 1978 (Box 607, Folder 19)
          - Final Reports, 1979 (Box 607, Folder 20)
          - Jo Sickbert Day Event Reports, 1978 (Box 608, Folder 1)
      - Sports and Fitness
        - Merrill Lynch Olympic Spirit Program, 1998 (Box 608, Folder 2)
        - National Girls and Women in Sports Day, 1990-99 (Box 608, Folder 3-6)
        - National Girls Tennis Program, 1990-91 (Box 608, Folder 7)
        - National YWCA Swimming Championships, 1970-73, 1989-90, 1999, n.d. (Box 608, Folder 8-10)
        - Peter Westbrook Fencing Program, YWCA and Peter Westbrook Foundation, 1994-99 (Box 608, Folder 11-12)
        - Women's Basketball: A Developmental Program, American Basketball Council in Cooperation with YWCA: manual, circa 1988 (Box 608, Folder 13)
        - YWCA of the USA/Nike Sports and Fitness Project
          - General, 1994-98 (Box 608, Folder 14-16)
          - The YWCA P.L.A.Y.ground, 1998-99 (Box 608, Folder 17)
          - Basketball Program grants
            - General, 1995-99, n.d. (Box 609, Folder 1)
            - Train the Trainers Workshop, Dec 1997 (Box 609, Folder 2)
            - Arizona: Maricopa County (Phoenix)
              - General, 1997-99 (Box 609, Folder 3)
              - Player evaluation forms (Box 609, Folder 4)
            - California
              - Glendale, 1997-98 (Box 609, Folder 5)
              - Central Orange County, 1995-97 (Box 609, Folder 6)
              - Pasadena Foothill Valley, 1999 (Box 609, Folder 7)
              - San Francisco, 1995-97 (Box 609, Folder 8)
              - Santa Monica, 1993-99 (Box 609, Folder 9)
            - Florida: Miami, 1995-98 (Box 609, Folder 10)
            - Illinois
              - McLean County (Bloomington), 1996-99 (Box 609, Folder 11)
              - Rockford, 1996-97 (Box 609, Folder 12)
            - Indiana: Kokomo, 1995-97 (Box 609, Folder 13)
            - Iowa
              - Black Hawk County (Waterloo), 1996-99 (Box 610, Folder 1)
              - Greater Des Moines, 1996 (Box 610, Folder 2)
            - Kansas: Salina, 1998-99 (Box 610, Folder 3)
            - Louisiana: Shreveport, 1995-97 (Box 610, Folder 4)
            - Maine
              - Bangor-Brewer, 1996 (Box 610, Folder 5)
              - Portland, 1995-99 (Box 610, Folder 6)
            - Maryland: Greater Baltimore, 1995-97 (Box 610, Folder 7)
            - Massachusetts: Greater Lawrence, 1997-98 (Box 610, Folder 8)
            - Michigan
              - Bay County, 1998-99 (Box 610, Folder 9)
              - Greater Lansing, 1996-98 (Box 610, Folder 10)
            - Minnesota: St. Paul, 1996 (Box 610, Folder 11)
            - Missouri
              - Kansas City, 1995-98 (Box 610, Folder 12)
              - St. Louis, 1998-99 (Box 610, Folder 13)
            - New Jersey: Trenton, 1995-97 (Box 610, Folder 14)
            - New Mexico: Albuquerque, 1995-97 (Box 610, Folder 15)
            - New York
              - Adirondack Foothills, 1998-99 (Box 610, Folder 16)
              - Brooklyn, 1996 (Box 610, Folder 17)
              - Elmira, 1996-97 (Box 610, Folder 18)
              - Lockport, 1995-97 (Box 610, Folder 19)
              - Schenectady, 1995-96 (Box 610, Folder 20)
              - Western New York (Buffalo), 1995-97 (Box 610, Folder 21)
              - White Plains and Central Westchester, 1996-98 (Box 610, Folder 22)
            - North Carolina
              - Asheville, 1995-97 (Box 610, Folder 23)
              - Central Carolinas (Charlotte)
                - General, 1996-99 (Box 611, Folder 1)
                - Player Evaluation Forms, 1998 (Box 611, Folder 2)
              - Greensboro, 1998 (Box 611, Folder 3)
              - Rocky Mount, 1997-98 (Box 611, Folder 4)
            - Ohio
              - Cincinnati
                - General, 1996-99 (Box 611, Folder 5-7)
                - Basketball Clinic, Mar 1997 (Box 611, Folder 8)
                - Evaluations, n.d. (Box 611, Folder 9)
              - Cleveland, 1995-99 (Box 611, Folder 10-11)
              - Columbus, 1995-97 (Box 611, Folder 12)
              - Dayton, 1997-98 (Box 611, Folder 13)
              - Lorain, 1995-97 (Box 612, Folder 1)
              - Summit County (Akron), 1997-98 (Box 612, Folder 2)
              - Youngstown, 1998-99 (Box 612, Folder 3)
            - Oklahoma: Enid, 1995-96 (Box 612, Folder 4)
            - Oregon: Portland, 1995-97 (Box 612, Folder 5)
            - Pennsylvania
              - Gettysburg, 1995-98 (Box 612, Folder 6)
              - Greater West Chester, 1995-96 (Box 612, Folder 7)
              - York, 1998-99 (Box 612, Folder 8)
            - South Carolina: Greenville, 1995-99 (Box 612, Folder 9-10)
            - South Dakota: Sioux Falls, 1998 (Box 612, Folder 11)
            - Tennessee: Knoxville, 1997-99 (Box 612, Folder 12)
            - Texas
              - Abilene, 1996 (Box 612, Folder 13)
              - Dallas, 1995-97 (Box 612, Folder 14)
              - Lubbock, 1997-99 (Box 612, Folder 15)
              - Paris and Lamar County, 1995-96 (Box 612, Folder 16)
              - San Antonio, 1995-98 (Box 612, Folder 17-18)
            - Utah: Salt Lake City, 1997-98 (Box 612, Folder 19)
            - Virginia: Lynchburg, 1995-96 (Box 613, Folder 1)
            - Washington
              - Seattle, 1996-97 (Box 613, Folder 2)
              - Yakima, 1996 (Box 613, Folder 3)
            - West Virginia: Wheeling, 1994-97 (Box 613, Folder 4)
            - Wisconsin
              - Racine, 1996-98 (Box 613, Folder 5)
              - Christoph Memorial (Waukesha), 1995-96 (Box 613, Folder 6)
          - Volleyball Program grants
            - General, 1994-98 (Box 613, Folder 7)
            - Arkansas: El Dorado, 1996-99 (Box 613, Folder 8)
            - California
              - Central Orange County, 1996-97 (Box 613, Folder 9)
              - San Francisco, 1996-97 (Box 613, Folder 10)
              - Santa Monica, 1998-99 (Box 613, Folder 11)
            - Florida: Miami, 1996 (Box 613, Folder 12)
            - Georgia: Macon, 1995-98 (Box 613, Folder 13)
            - Illinois
              - Aurora, 1998-99 (Box 613, Folder 14)
              - Freeport, 1996 (Box 613, Folder 15)
              - McClean County (Bloomington), 1997-98 (Box 613, Folder 16)
            - Indiana: Muncie, 1996 (Box 613, Folder 17)
            - Iowa: Marshalltown, 1996 (Box 613, Folder 18)
            - Kentucky: Lexington, 1996-98 (Box 613, Folder 19)
            - Louisiana: Baton Rouge, 1996-97 (Box 613, Folder 20)
            - Maine: Portland, 1998-99 (Box 613, Folder 21)
            - Massachusetts: Greater Lawrence, 1998-99 (Box 613, Folder 22)
            - Minnesota
              - Duluth, 1996 (Box 613, Folder 23)
              - St. Paul, 1996 (Box 613, Folder 24)
            - New York
              - Binghampton and Broome County, 1996-98 (Box 613, Folder 25)
              - Mohawk Valley, 1996 (Box 613, Folder 26)
              - Schenectady, 1996 (Box 613, Folder 27)
              - Western New York (Buffalo), 1996 (Box 613, Folder 28)
            - North Carolina
              - Central Carolinas (Charlotte), 1996-99 (Box 613, Folder 29)
              - High Point, 1996-99 (Box 614, Folder 1)
            - Ohio
              - Cincinnati
                - General, 1996-99 (Box 614, Folder 2)
                - Player Evaluation Forms, n.d. (Box 614, Folder 3)
              - Cleveland, 1996-97 (Box 614, Folder 4)
              - Columbus, 1997-98 (Box 614, Folder 5)
              - Summit County, 1996 (Box 614, Folder 6)
            - Oklahoma: Enid, 1998-99 (Box 614, Folder 7)
            - Pennsylvania
              - Bethlehem, 1996-97 (Box 614, Folder 8)
              - Gettysburg and Adams County, 1996-97 (Box 614, Folder 9)
            - Rhode Island: Northern RI (Woonsocket), 1997-2000 (Box 614, Folder 10)
            - South Carolina: Greenville, 1996-98 (Box 614, Folder 11)
            - South Dakota: Sioux Falls, 1996-99 (Box 614, Folder 12)
            - Tennessee: Knoxville, 1996-97 (Box 614, Folder 13)
            - Texas: San Antonio, 1996 (Box 614, Folder 14)
            - Washington: Spokane, 1997-98 (Box 614, Folder 15)
            - Wisconsin
              - Racine, 1996-98 (Box 614, Folder 16)
              - Christoph Memorial (Waukesha), 1996-99 (Box 614, Folder 17)
          - "New Face of Fitness" Fitness Training Program
            - General
              - 1995-96 (Box 614, Folder 18-19)
              - 1997 (Box 615, Folder 1)
            - Arkansas: El Dorado, 1996-97 (Box 615, Folder 2)
            - California
              - Glendale, 1996-97 (Box 615, Folder 3)
              - Central Orange County, 1995-97 (Box 615, Folder 4)
              - Santa Monica, 1995-96 (Box 615, Folder 5)
            - Delaware: New Castle County, 1996-97 (Box 615, Folder 6)
            - Georgia
              - Greater Atlanta, 1997 (Box 615, Folder 7)
              - Augusta, 1996 (Box 615, Folder 8)
            - Hawaii
              - Hawaii Island, 1996-97 (Box 615, Folder 9)
              - Kauai County, 1995-97 (Box 615, Folder 10)
              - O'ahu, 1996-97 (Box 615, Folder 11)
            - Illinois
              - McClean County (Bloomington), 1996-97 (Box 615, Folder 12)
              - Rockford, 1996-97 (Box 615, Folder 13)
              - Lake and McHenry Counties (Waukegan), 1995-96 (Box 615, Folder 14)
            - Indiana: Greater Lafayette, 1996 (Box 615, Folder 15)
            - Iowa
              - Des Moines, 1995-97 (Box 615, Folder 16)
              - Washington, 1996 (Box 615, Folder 17)
            - Kansas: Topeka, 1995-96 (Box 615, Folder 18)
            - Maine: Portland, 1995-97 (Box 615, Folder 19)
            - Maryland: Annapolis and Anne Arundel County, 1996-97 (Box 615, Folder 20)
            - Massachusetts: Newburyport, 1995-96 (Box 615, Folder 21)
            - Michigan: Kalamazoo, 1996 (Box 615, Folder 22)
            - Minnesota: Minneapolis, 1995-96 (Box 615, Folder 23)
            - Missouri: St. Louis, 1996-97 (Box 615, Folder 24)
            - Nebraska: Lincoln, 1995-96 (Box 615, Folder 25)
            - New Jersey